Hirsh Health Sciences Library Records UA225
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Slide library, 1893 -- 1998; UA225.004; 1.2 Linear Feet; 937 Digital Object(s)
  - Presidents, Deans, Faculty, 1902 -- 1994; UA225.004.001.00003; Tufts University School of Medicine
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, Portrait Unveiling, 1980-01-23; UA225.004.001.00003.00127; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Douglas Thorn, UA225.004.001.00003.00128; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Thorn, Douglas
    - Dr. Jackson Thomas, UA225.004.001.00003.00129; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Thomas, Jackson M.
    - Dr. Bryan Toole, UA225.004.001.00003.00130; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Toole, Bryan P.
    - Dr. Bryan Toole, UA225.004.001.00003.00131; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Sheldon Wolff, graduation at Vanderbilt, UA225.004.001.00003.00132; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Vanderbilt University; Commencement ceremonies; Slides (photographs); Wolff, Sheldon M.
    - Dr. Sheldon Wolff, UA225.004.001.00003.00133; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, in commencement attire
      Slides (photographs); Wolff, Sheldon M.
    - Dr. Sheldon Wolff, UA225.004.001.00003.00134; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Sheldon Wolff, UA225.004.001.00003.00135; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Sheldon Wolff, UA225.004.001.00003.00136; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Sheldon Wolff, UA225.004.001.00003.00137; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, labwork with another person
    - Dr. Henry Wortis, UA225.004.001.00003.00138; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, labwork looking at mouse/rat with another woman
      Slides (photographs); Wortis, Henry
    - Dr. Robert Sarno, UA225.004.001.00003.00139; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, two people performing scan on a patient
      Slides (photographs); Sarno, Robert
    - Dr. Robert Sarno, UA225.004.001.00003.00140; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Robert Sarno, UA225.004.001.00003.00141; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Robert Sarno, UA225.004.001.00003.00142; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Robert Sarno, UA225.004.001.00003.00143; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Robert Sarno, UA225.004.001.00003.00144; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Robert Sarno, UA225.004.001.00003.00145; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. John Kauer, UA225.004.001.00003.00146; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, two people looking at molecule recplicas
      Slides (photographs); Kauer, John
    - Dr. Louis Lasagna, Sackler School Dean, UA225.004.001.00003.00147; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Deans (Education); Slides (photographs); Lasagna, Louis
    - Dr. John Harrington, TUSM Dean, UA225.004.001.00003.00148; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Deans (Education); Slides (photographs); Harrington, John T.
  - Departments and Divisions, Research, Programs, Finances, Fund Raising and Governance, 1950 -- 1993; UA225.004.001.00004; Tufts University School of Medicine
    - Dr. Henry Banks and Al Ingram, Orthopedic Surgery, UA225.004.001.00004.00001; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Banks, Henry H. (1921-); Ingram, Al
    - Dr. Henry Banks et al. on rounds, 1975-01-22; UA225.004.001.00004.00002; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Henry Banks et al. on rounds, UA225.004.001.00004.00003; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Drs. Banks, Axer, and Zancolli, UA225.004.001.00004.00004; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Slides (photographs); Banks, Henry H. (1921-); Axer, Anatol; Zancolli, Eduardo?
    - Drs. Henry Banks, Stuart Belkin, and John Harris, UA225.004.001.00004.00005; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Slides (photographs); Banks, Henry H. (1921-); Belkin, Stuart C.; Harris, John
    - Dr. Stuart Belkin and injured Tufts athlete, 1977 -- 1978; UA225.004.001.00004.00006; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, football
      Physicians; Athletes; African Americans; Slides (photographs); Belkin, Stuart C.
    - Drs. Donald Booth and Lawrence Crane at Maine Medical Center, UA225.004.001.00004.00007; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Maine.; Teaching Hospitals; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Booth, Donald; Crane, Lawrence; Maine Medical Center
    - Dr. William Cashman, UA225.004.001.00004.00008; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, with scans (x-rays)
      Orthopedics; Radiology; Physicians; Spine; Slides (photographs); Cashman, William F.
    - Drs. Hubert Wolfe and Jonathan Cohen in orthopedic pathology course, UA225.004.001.00004.00009; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Orthopedics; Pathology; Physicians; Medical instruments and apparatus; Slides (photographs); Wolfe, Hubert; Cohen, Jonathan, 1915-2003
    - Drs. Jonathan Cohen and Mohinder Mital, UA225.004.001.00004.00010; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, talking to each other
      Physicians; Medical literature; Slides (photographs); Cohen, Jonathan, 1915-2003; Mital, Mohinder A.
    - Dr. Clifford Craig, UA225.004.001.00004.00011; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Pediatrics; Slides (photographs); Craig, Clifford L.
    - Dr. Clifford Craig, UA225.004.001.00004.00012; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Littler and Dr. Eaton, UA225.004.001.00004.00013; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Orthopedics; Medical literature; Hand; Models, Anatomic; Slides (photographs); Littler, William J.; Eaton, Elizabeth K.
    - Dr. William Donaldson, UA225.004.001.00004.00014; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, with microscope
      Physicians; Microscopes; Slides (photographs); Donaldson, William R.
    - Dr. William Donaldson, UA225.004.001.00004.00015; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Banks et al. on rounds, UA225.004.001.00004.00016; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, examination in group
      Physicians; Teaching rounds; Orthopedics; Traction; Slides (photographs); Banks, Henry H. (1921-)
    - Dr. Goldberg at Rene Devila, UA225.004.001.00004.00017; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; African Americans; Nurses; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Goldberg, Michael J.
    - Dr. Michael Goldberg, UA225.004.001.00004.00018; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Michael Goldberg, UA225.004.001.00004.00019; Tufts University (Box 1)
      [duplicate]; Slides (photographs); Goldberg, Michael J.
    - Dr. Joseph Ferrone, student, and patient, UA225.004.001.00004.00020; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Medical students; Orthopedics; Pediatrics; Hand; Slides (photographs); Ferrone, Joseph D.
    - Dr. Joseph Ferrone, student, and patient, UA225.004.001.00004.00021; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. William Green, UA225.004.001.00004.00022; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Orthopedics; Pediatrics; Slides (photographs); Green, William T.
    - Dr. Michael Goldberg, UA225.004.001.00004.00023; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Orthopedics; Pediatrics; Slides (photographs); Goldberg, Michael J.
    - Dr. Goldberg at Rene Devila, UA225.004.001.00004.00024; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; African Americans; Nurses; Orthopedics; Pediatrics; Spine; Slides (photographs); Goldberg, Michael J.
    - Dr. Baty on pediatric rounds with patients and students, UA225.004.001.00004.00025; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Pediatrics; Orthopedics; Teaching rounds; Medical students; Slides (photographs); Baty, James M.
    - Dr. John Harris and Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, UA225.004.001.00004.00026; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Orthopedics; Medical literature; Slides (photographs); Harris, John; Thibodeau, Arthur A.
    - Dr. Malcom Meyn, UA225.004.001.00004.00027; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Medical instruments and apparatus; Physical Examination; Slides (photographs); Meyn, Malcolm
    - Dr. Malcom Meyn, UA225.004.001.00004.00028; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, examination on patient
      Physicians; Orthopedics; Physical Examination; Slides (photographs); Meyn, Malcolm
    - Dr. Lewis Millender, UA225.004.001.00004.00029; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Millender, Lewis
    - Dr. Mohinder Mital, UA225.004.001.00004.00030; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Mital, Mohinder A.
    - Dr. Won Oh, UA225.004.001.00004.00031; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Oh, Won
    - Dr. Won Oh, P. T. Lecture, UA225.004.001.00004.00032; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Teaching; Physical Therapists; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Oh, Won
    - Dr. Lawrence Karlin, UA225.004.001.00004.00033; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Karlin, Lawrence I.
    - Dr. Leonard Ruby, UA225.004.001.00004.00034; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Hand; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Ruby, Leonard
    - Dr. Leonard Ruby, UA225.004.001.00004.00035; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Thomas Quigley, UA225.004.001.00004.00036; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Slides (photographs); Quigley, Thomas B.
    - Dr. William Sullivan, UA225.004.001.00004.00037; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Nurses; Slides (photographs); Sullivan, William
    - Dr. William Sullivan, UA225.004.001.00004.00038; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Slides (photographs); Sullivan, William
    - Dr. Seymour Zimbler, UA225.004.001.00004.00039; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Zimbler, Seymour
    - Dr. Seymour Zimbler, UA225.004.001.00004.00040; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, leture
      Physicians; Teaching; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Zimbler, Seymour
    - Dr. Seymour Zimbler, UA225.004.001.00004.00041; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Seymour Zimbler, UA225.004.001.00004.00042; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Image of newspaper, "The Boston Herald American" Thursday, Feb 16, 1978
      Physicians; Fracture fixation; Pediatrics; Wounds and injuries; Slides (photographs); Zimbler, Seymour; New England Medical Center; Boston Herald American
    - Dr. Albert Ferguson and first Thibodeau lecture, UA225.004.001.00004.00043; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, audience lecture
      Physicians; Orthopedics; Auditoriums; Slides (photographs); Ferguson, Albert; Thibodeau, Arthur A.
    - Dr. Thibodeau Lecture (Dr. Harris), 1975-04; UA225.004.001.00004.00044; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, listening to lecture
      Orthopedics; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Thibodeau, Arthur A.; Harris, John
    - Drs. Arthur Thibodeau, Philip Wilson, Henry Banks, and William Green, UA225.004.001.00004.00045; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Orthopedics; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Thibodeau, Arthur A.; Wilson, Philip; Banks, Henry H. (1921-); Green, William T.
    - NEMC residents and staff, 1973; UA225.004.001.00004.00046; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Internship and residency; Physicians; Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs)
    - NEMC residents and staff, 1974; UA225.004.001.00004.00047; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Staff, 1975; UA225.004.001.00004.00048; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo. Back row, first on the left: Dr. Malcolm A Meyn, Jr.
      Orthopedics; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Meyn, Malcolm
    - Staff, 1975; UA225.004.001.00004.00049; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Second from left: Dr. Malcolm A Meyn, Jr.
    - Walk Rounds with Dr. Henry Banks, 1975-01-22; UA225.004.001.00004.00050; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, group looking at scans
      Orthopedics; Physicians; Teaching Hospitals; Teaching rounds; Slides (photographs); Banks, Henry H. (1921-)
    - Walk Rounds with Dr. Henry Banks, 1975-01-22; UA225.004.001.00004.00051; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Walk Rounds with Dr. Henry Banks, 1975-01-22; UA225.004.001.00004.00052; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Walk Rounds with Dr. Henry Banks, 1975-01-22; UA225.004.001.00004.00053; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Walk Rounds with Dr. Henry Banks, 1975-01-22; UA225.004.001.00004.00054; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, explaing scan
      Orthopedics; Physicians; Teaching Hospitals; Teaching rounds; Radiology; Slides (photographs); Banks, Henry H. (1921-)
    - Dr. Thomas B. Quigley, 1975-02-04; UA225.004.001.00004.00055; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Teaching; Internship and residency; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Quigley, Thomas B.
    - Dr. Thomas B. Quigley and Fx. Review, 1975-02-19; UA225.004.001.00004.00056; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Teaching; Internship and residency; Physicians; Radiology; Slides (photographs); Quigley, Thomas B.
    - Dr. Thomas B. Quigley and Fx. Review, 1975-02-19; UA225.004.001.00004.00057; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Drs. Albert Ferguson, Jonathan Cohen and Henry Banks at Kennedy Memorial Hospital rounds, UA225.004.001.00004.00058; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, audience
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching; Internship and residency; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Ferguson, Albert; Cohen, Jonathan, 1915-2003; Banks, Henry H. (1921-)
    - Drs. Jonathan Cohen, Michael Bonfiglio, and Henry Banks at Kennedy Memorial Hospital rounds, UA225.004.001.00004.00059; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching; Internship and residency; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Cohen, Jonathan, 1915-2003; Bonfiglio, Michael; Banks, Henry H. (1921-)
    - Dr. Henry Banks and Dr. Jonathan Cohen, UA225.004.001.00004.00060; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Teaching; Internship and residency; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Banks, Henry H. (1921-); Cohen, Jonathan, 1915-2003
    - Staff and Residents, 1977; UA225.004.001.00004.00061; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Internship and residency; Staff; Slides (photographs)
    - Staff and Residents, 1979; UA225.004.001.00004.00062; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Drs. Harold Freedman, John Park, and Mark Belsky at New Orleans AAOS, 1982-04; UA225.004.001.00004.00063; Tufts University (Box 1)
      New Orleans.; Orthopedics; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Freedman, Harold; Park, John; Belsky, Mark R.
    - Dr. Laurence Schenk and Dr. John Kazes at New Orleans AAOS, 1982-04; UA225.004.001.00004.00064; Tufts University (Box 1)
      New Orleans.; Orthopedics; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Schenk, Laurence; Kazes, John
    - Dr. Harold Freedman and Dr. Vincent Iacono at New Orleans AAOS, 1982-04; UA225.004.001.00004.00065; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, at dinner table
      New Orleans.; Orthopedics; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Freedman, Harold; Iacono, Vincent
    - Dr. and Mrs. Ed Nalebuff at New Orleans AAOS, 1982-04; UA225.004.001.00004.00066; Tufts University (Box 1)
      New Orleans.; Orthopedics; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Nalebuff, Edward
    - Dr. Mark Belsky, UA225.004.001.00004.00067; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Orthopedics; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Belsky, Mark R.
    - Dr. Roderick Turner, UA225.004.001.00004.00068; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Orthopedics; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Turner, Roderick
    - Dr. Benjamin Bierbaum, UA225.004.001.00004.00069; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Orthopedics; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Bierbaum, Benjamin E.
    - Dr. Otto Aufranc, UA225.004.001.00004.00070; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Orthopedics; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Aufranc, Otto
    - Orthopedic laboratory in Rehabilitation Building, UA225.004.001.00004.00071; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo of lab
      Boston (Mass.); Laboratories; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); New England Medical Center
    - Orthopedic laboratory in Rehabilitation Building, UA225.004.001.00004.00072; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Orthopedic laboratory in Rehabilitation Building, UA225.004.001.00004.00073; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo of lab, person working
      Boston (Mass.); Laboratories; Orthopedics; Microscopes; Slides (photographs); New England Medical Center
    - Orthopedic laboratory in Rehabilitation Building, UA225.004.001.00004.00074; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Orthopedic laboratory on M & V 2, UA225.004.001.00004.00075; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Laboratories; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Medical and Veterinary Building
    - Orthopedic laboratory on M & V 2, UA225.004.001.00004.00076; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Orthopedic laboratory on M & V 2, UA225.004.001.00004.00077; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston pathology course for orthopedic residents, UA225.004.001.00004.00078; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Students at microscopes
      Internship and residency; Orthopedics; Pathology; Microscopes; Slides (photographs)
    - Boston pathology course for orthopedic residents, UA225.004.001.00004.00079; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Posner open house, UA225.004.001.00004.00080; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, building
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); New England Medical Center
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, 11 Nassau, UA225.004.001.00004.00081; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, 1975; UA225.004.001.00004.00082; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, building entrance
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, UA225.004.001.00004.00083; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Reception Area, 1st Floor, 1979; UA225.004.001.00004.00084; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, two people in office
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Waiting Room, 1st Floor, 1979; UA225.004.001.00004.00085; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, two people in [lounge]?
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Exam Room, 1st Floor, 1979; UA225.004.001.00004.00086; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo of room
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Dictating Room, 1st Floor, 1979; UA225.004.001.00004.00087; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, man looking at scan
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Exam Room, Basement, UA225.004.001.00004.00088; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo of examination room
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Plaster Room, Basement, UA225.004.001.00004.00089; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, X-Ray Waiting Area, Basement, UA225.004.001.00004.00090; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, X-Ray, Basement (Cindy), UA225.004.001.00004.00091; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo of person examination room
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Dr. Zimbler, 2nd floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00092; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo of office
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Dr. Oh, 2nd floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00093; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Bookkeeping, 2nd floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00094; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo of people in office
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Bookkeeping, 2nd floor (Jo), UA225.004.001.00004.00095; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Dr. Ferrone's sec'y., 3rd floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00096; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Dr. Goldberg, 3rd floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00097; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Dr. Harris, 4th floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00098; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Dr. Donaldson, 4th floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00099; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Dr. Ruby, 4th floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00100; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, Library, 4th floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00101; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Hemenway Building for orthopedic patients and orthopedic staff at New England Medical Center, move to Posner, 1979-05-31; UA225.004.001.00004.00102; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, outside of building
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, 1983-01-12; UA225.004.001.00004.00103; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); Posner Hall; Boston Campus
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, ramp, 1983-01-12; UA225.004.001.00004.00104; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, outside of building, patient pushed in wheelchair
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, reception desk (Lula), UA225.004.001.00004.00105; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, person in office
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Waiting Area, 1st Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00106; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, people in lounge
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Elevator, 1st Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00107; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, inside building
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Waiting Area, Basement, UA225.004.001.00004.00108; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, room inside building
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, X-Ray, Basement, UA225.004.001.00004.00109; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, scan room
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Plaster Room, Basement, UA225.004.001.00004.00110; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, room
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Waiting Room, 2nd Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00111; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, patient waiting room
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Exam Room, UA225.004.001.00004.00112; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, examination room
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Treatment Room, 2nd Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00113; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Growth Study, UA225.004.001.00004.00114; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Dr. Ruby's Office, 2nd Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00115; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); Ruby, Leonard; Posner Hall; Boston Campus
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Dr. Zimbler's Office, 3rd Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00116; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, office
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); Zimbler, Seymour; Posner Hall; Boston Campus
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Dr. Ferrone's Office, 3rd Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00117; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); Ferrone, Joseph D.; Posner Hall; Boston Campus